<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fly</title><link>https://blog.flysan.xyz/</link><description>Recent content on fly</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 21:13:53 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.flysan.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sitting on the floor</title><link>https://blog.flysan.xyz/blog/sitting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 21:13:53 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.flysan.xyz/blog/sitting/</guid><description>Recently a friend asked:
Hm what&amp;rsquo;s the psychological explanation behind sitting on the floor being so calming
I don&amp;rsquo;t think there&amp;rsquo;s necessarily a single explanation for that, but my first guess was that it had to do with the fact floors are generally cold, uncomfy and dirty. As opposed to a chair, you need to make a conscious decision to actually sit down on the floor, but when you embrace it you might find some comfort.</description></item><item><title>fly</title><link>https://blog.flysan.xyz/blog/fly/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 21:20:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.flysan.xyz/blog/fly/</guid><description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m fly, and this is my blog!
🐱‍🐉 I like challenging things (sometimes) 🐱‍💻 I study Computer Science @TUM 🐱‍👤 I&amp;rsquo;m learning Python, Lua, Java, Javascript, C, OCaml, x86 ASM 🐱‍🏍 I love problem solving and programming - but most importantly: I love cats! If that doesn&amp;rsquo;t sound like me, you&amp;rsquo;re probably have the wrong person!</description></item><item><title>Dune</title><link>https://blog.flysan.xyz/quotes/books/dune/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.flysan.xyz/quotes/books/dune/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;He wanted you to know he never suspected you. He wanted you to know he always trusted you completely. Always loved you and trusted you. He said he would have sooner mistrusted himself. And he had but one regret: that he never made you his duchess.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ndash; Paul Atreides, from Dune, Book One, Frank Herbert</description></item><item><title>latex test</title><link>https://blog.flysan.xyz/blog/latex/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.flysan.xyz/blog/latex/</guid><description>hello \(e = mc^2\)
$$ \frac{5}{3} $$</description></item><item><title>Love everything regardless</title><link>https://blog.flysan.xyz/quotes/misc/i-love-you/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.flysan.xyz/quotes/misc/i-love-you/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Your life is not bound by labels, nor is it bound by expectation. You simply are. It is only when we rid ourselves of labels we&amp;rsquo;ve been given since we were born, that we can begin to truly be. When we begin to treat what&amp;rsquo;s around us with love, we can find it in our hearts to love ourselves as well. What you have gone through, the pain you have felt, does not go to waste.</description></item><item><title>Short quotes</title><link>https://blog.flysan.xyz/quotes/misc/shorts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.flysan.xyz/quotes/misc/shorts/</guid><description>These quotes were too short, or could not be attributed to a single author, to warrant a single post, so I have compiled them here!
&amp;ldquo;The beginning of life is also the start of death&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Life isn&amp;rsquo;t as easy as you think it is, but it&amp;rsquo;s not as hard as people say it is&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Circunda-te de rosas, ama, bebe e cala.
O mais é nada.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; Fernando Pessoa
We shall not cease from exploration And the end of all our exploring Will be to arrive where we started And know the place for the first time.</description></item><item><title>Videos that live rent free in my mind</title><link>https://blog.flysan.xyz/misc/videos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.flysan.xyz/misc/videos/</guid><description>Here is a compilation of videos which always put a smile, or tears, on my face, and maybe on yours too! They may be memes, playlists, songs or just nice videos.
Alpha by C418 is one of the nicest videogame OST pieces out there, and together with the End Poem by Julian Gough makes up my favorite artistic compositions of all time. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in the story behind the poem, &amp;ldquo;I wrote a story for a friend&amp;rdquo; talks about it.</description></item></channel></rss>