<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on fly</title><link>https://blog.flysan.xyz/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on fly</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 21:20:42 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.flysan.xyz/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>On social media</title><link>https://blog.flysan.xyz/blog/on_social_media/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 19:38:56 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.flysan.xyz/blog/on_social_media/</guid><description>Recently a friend asked:
Hm what&amp;rsquo;s the psychological explanation behind sitting on the floor being so calming
For one, the ease of access to information and communication has transformed human life in ways no one could have predicted or imagined even just a century ago. Global real time communication means we are constantly being fed information every second of our lives, from everywhere, often at the same time. If the first industrial revolution had brought anonymity to society, the third and fourth have brought exposure: we have the ability to literally summon knowledge from all over the world, at the palm of our hands, in a matter of seconds, all the while watching your favorite netflix series.</description></item><item><title>Sitting on the floor</title><link>https://blog.flysan.xyz/blog/sitting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 21:13:53 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.flysan.xyz/blog/sitting/</guid><description>Recently a friend asked:
How can I be so low-energy when I&amp;rsquo;ve done almost nothing productive for the last week?
I don&amp;rsquo;t think there&amp;rsquo;s necessarily a single explanation for that, but my first guess was that it had to do with the fact floors are generally cold, uncomfy and dirty. As opposed to a chair, you need to make a conscious decision to actually sit down on the floor, but when you embrace it you might find some comfort.</description></item><item><title>fly</title><link>https://blog.flysan.xyz/blog/fly/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 21:20:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.flysan.xyz/blog/fly/</guid><description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m fly, and this is my blog!
🐱‍🐉 I like challenging things (sometimes) 🐱‍💻 I study Computer Science @TUM 🐱‍👤 I&amp;rsquo;m learning Python, Lua, Java, Javascript, C, OCaml, x86 ASM 🐱‍🏍 I love problem solving and programming - but most importantly: I love cats! If that doesn&amp;rsquo;t sound like me, you&amp;rsquo;re probably have the wrong person!</description></item><item><title>latex test</title><link>https://blog.flysan.xyz/blog/latex/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.flysan.xyz/blog/latex/</guid><description>hello \(e = mc^2\)
$$ \frac{5}{3} $$</description></item></channel></rss>